All right, we do have Anthony Smith on
the line. Anthony, congratulations on
this moment. I know it's a proud day for
you and your family. Take us through uh
what's going through your head right now
as you are now a member of the Dallas
Cowboys.
>> Yes, sir, man. Well, shoot. The first
thing I just want to give it to God,
man. Like without him, I wouldn't be in
this position, man. All the struggles,
all the all the trials and tribulations
I done went through in college and my
family and stuff. And shoot, he brought
me out on the other side. So for me and
my family, man, this is this is an
ecstatic moment, bro. I can't lie. So
I'm feeling good, man. My fans feeling
good. I'm just ready to get down to
Dallas and play some ball, man.
>> Anthony, you and I have actually talked
a couple times during my time covering
the American Conference, and I've been a
big fan of your game for quite some
time. For those at the NFL level or the
Dallas Cowboys level that may not know,
tell them what they're getting in
Anthony Smith as a wide receiver at the
next level.
>> Shoot. I know they're getting somebody
who can take the top off the defense,
somebody who's fast, and somebody who
loves to compete, ready to work every
day. So, shoot, just as a receiver, man,
I'm ready to just go get it.
>> Hey, Anthony, congratulations. Walk me
through the emotions of the weekend. Did
you expect to be picked coming in? And
then when you finally got the phone
call, just talk me through the relief in
the moment.
>> Yeah, man. So, shoot. I I mean, I did
have that faith, man, that I was going
to get picked this weekend. Just just
having that hope. Um, and then as the
weekend went off, went on and stuff like
that, I just seen the rounds go on and
on and stuff like that. And, um, I still
kept that hope, my family still kept
that hope that I was gonna get drafted.
Um, and then me and my agent had talked
and stuff like that. And, um, we were
kind of prepared to go to the UDFA
route. And then, um, the Cowboys had
called me, man, and, uh, walked
downstairs with my family and and told
them who I was on the phone with and
stuff. And I got a lot of family who's
Dallas fans. So, when they heard that I
was on the phone with you guys, ready to
get drafted, they were they were so
excited, man. So, for me and my family,
bro, it's just like it's a crazy
process. It's a long process, but it it
was all worth it, bro. For sure.
>> And then you'll be reuniting with Savone
Revel Jr., uh, have you talked to Vaughn
yet? Has he shot you a text?
>> He hasn't. He hasn't just yet, but me
and him talked the other day, though,
man. Me and him talked the other day
just about like um being at the next
level, things to expect and stuff like
that, and the work that you got to put
in. And um I mean he's been there for a
year so he's been pouring into me
knowing that um this is my goal that I
want to get to the NFL and I want to
play in the NFL. Um so like him just
pouring into me and just letting me know
the things that I need to get right and
and check off the box um so that I can
make those things happen. So that's
that's my good man for sure. As you
reflect back at at your college journey
and in going from NC State to Eastern
Carolina, it seems like it kind of like
you had to go through maybe some
struggles there at NC State and then
finally blossom there at East Carolina.
What really stood out to you about that
and kind of helped you to become the
receiver you are now?
>> Yeah, I mean for me, bro, is really just
maturity and intentionality, man. Um,
just just getting older, you know what
I'm saying? Learning how to how to
really play ball and how to really, you
know what I'm saying? the ins and outs
of the offense and stuff like that. And
then um the intentionality that every
day coming in coming in the building,
whether it's treatment, lift, um
conditioning, practice that I'm just
trying to attack it, um shoot, won't get
1% better each day, man. Just attack it
head on. Um and just compete at
everything I do, man. So,
>> you also seem to have an outstanding
hair game, Anthony. [laughter] Uh what
goes into that?
>> Shoot. Not much, honestly. I mean,
shoot. I I uh I cut my hair not too long
ago. I used to have it super super long,
but I I cut it short now, so a little
bit more manageable, easy to maintain.
So,
>> that's just natural talent. That's all
it is.
>> Yeah, man. Just natural, bro. Just
natural.
[laughter]
>> Hey, Anthony, congratulations. Not sure
how I can transition to a much better
question there. Um, but [laughter]
you know, at at East Carolina, didn't
play special teams and rece
at the NFL level. How open are you to
that? And is that something that in in
whatever conversations you've had with
Dallas that they've discussed with you?
>> Yeah, man. I mean, shoot, for me, bro,
my goal is to play in the NFL, not just
make it. So, whether I get to play a
receiver, scout team, running back,
returner, front line on kickoff, for me,
it don't really matter, man. I just want
to just help the team win and make an
impact um wherever I can. So, for me,
man, I'm open to any and everything,
bro.
>> Anthony, talk to me about uh what the
Cowboys are getting from you off the
field. What do you like to do in your
free time outside of football? What kind
of person are you?
>> Shoot. For me, man, I'm a real chill,
relaxed person, man. I got two dogs. So,
for me, that's that's where I spend most
of my time when I'm not um at the
facilities or when I'm not doing
football. I'm usually outside the dog
park or laid up with my pups, man. So
that's uh that's something that shoot
that that's they've been ride or die on
me, man, since the NC State days. So
yeah, man. They get all my time when I'm
not doing ball, man.
>> What kind of dogs are they?
>> I got a lab retriever hound mix and then
I got a great pair of knees.
>> Oo, that's a lot of food. That's a lot
of food, man. Hey, good thing you're
getting a contract, man.
Congratulations. [laughter]
>> Hey, for real, though, bro. I appreciate
you, brother.
>> We We do have a a dog food sponsor, so
go ahead and just get on that. Oh, that
may come in handy.
>> Yeah, just just keep keep that in mind
whenever you get here to Dallas. What
are their names?
>> Yeah.
>> Uh my my girl, her name is Pinto and
then my boy, his name is Prince. So, two
P names, man.
>> Pento Prince. There you go. That's
awesome. Pinto Pince and a pirate, Mr.
Anthony Smith joining us here. Anthony,
thanks so much, man. We're excited to to
see you here in Dallas. safe travels and
we'll talk to you again next week.
>> Yes, sir. Man, I appreciate y'all so
much for getting on the call, man. See
y'all soon, bro.